<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?> 
<datafile xmlns:xs="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="wiitdb.xsd">
	<WiiTDB version="201812061554" games="36"/>
	<game name="1941 - Counter Attack">
		<id>39873A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>1941 - Counter Attack</title>
	<synopsis>The goal is to shoot down enemy airplanes and collect weapon power-ups (POW). One is only able to perform three loops per level and a bonus is awarded at the end of the level for unused loops. Player 1 uses a P-38 Lightning and Player 2 uses a Mosquito Mk IV. The game shifts from the original Pacific Front setting with that of the Western Front.

The game consists of six levels.

It was the first shoot 'em up to add +1 to the score when a continue is used.[1]</synopsis>
	<genre>Vertically scrolling shooters</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>1941 反击战</title>
		<synopsis>《1941 反 击 战》一 改 以 往 同 类 型 游 戏 中，玩 家 拥 有 若 干 架 飞 机 生 命 的 做 法，采 用 了 生 命 值 系 统 的 设 计，每 当 玩 家 被 击 中 时 就 损 失 一 格 生 命 值，当 生 命 值 为 0 时 则 游 戏 结 束，玩 家 可 以 选 择 是 否 投 币 继 续。游 戏 中 的 保 险 大 招 会 有 强 力 的 清 屏 效 果，但 代 价 是 损 失 一 格 生 命 值。

游 戏 一 共 有 六 大 关 卡：北 大 西 洋 上 空、欧 洲 港 口、V3 火 箭 基 地、布 兰 登 堡 大 门、大 平 原 和 敌 方 总 基 地。

虽 然 游 戏 名 称 里 的 年 份（1941）比 1942 要 早，但 是 这 款 游 戏 的 推 出 时 间 实 际 上 比《1942》要 晚 很 多，而 且 游 戏 的 内 容 似 乎 已 经 脱 离 二 战 题 材，改 走 未 来 战 争 的 路 线 了。

游 戏 的 蓄 力 系 统 和 宝 物 Power 等 的 设 计 跟《1942》和《1943》差 不 多，但 是 趣 味 性 和 难 度 有 所 提 升。玩 家 控 制 的 飞 机 也 很 有 个 性，可 以 沿 着 崖 壁 的 边 缘，象 个 风 车 一 样 旋 转 前 进。

关 卡 中 的 机 关 设 计 很 是 巧 妙，比 如 能 反 射 激 光 的 镜 子。Boss 团 里 的 战 斗 机、坦 克、装 甲 车，一 个 二 个 都 是 卡 普 空 STG 关 卡 的 招 牌 Boss，足 以 看 出 这 款 作 品 有 多 硬 核。</synopsis>
	<genre>纵向卷轴射击</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1990" month="02" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="16">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Adventure Quiz - Capcom World 2">
		<id>40781A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Adventure Quiz - Capcom World 2</title>
	<synopsis>Capcom World 2 - Adventure Quiz is a Japanese quiz game.</synopsis>
	<genre>Japanese Quiz</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>问答冒险 卡普空世界2</title>
		<synopsis>《问 答 冒 险 卡 普 空 世 界2》聚 集 了 很 多 卡 普 空 的 经 典 游 戏 人 物，加 上 富 有 创 意 的 剧 情，是 卡 普 空 公 司 相 当 具 有 纪 念 价 值 的 作 品。

游 戏 以 大 富 翁 走 格 子 的 方 式 进 行，目 的 要 打 倒 终 极 大 魔 王。不 过 由 于 这 是 一 款 问 答 游 戏，并 且 只 有 日 文 版 本，这 使 得 游 戏 的 受 众 非 常 有 限。

虽 然 游 戏 设 计 得 相 当 巧 妙，但 是 不 懂 日 文 就 无 福 消 受 了，推 荐 日 文 水 平 出 色 的 玩 家 尝 试。</synopsis>
		<genre>日语问答</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1992" month="09" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="10">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Cadillacs and Dinosaurs">
		<id>37360A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Cadillacs and Dinosaurs</title>
	<synopsis>Cadillacs and Dinosaurs: The Arcade Game, known in Japan as Cadillacs: Dinosaurs of a New Century is a 1993 arcade game released by Capcom. It is a side-scrolling beat 'em up based on the comic book series Xenozoic Tales. The game was produced as a tie-in to the Cadillacs and Dinosaurs animated series which was aired during the same year the game was released.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>恐龙快打</title>
		<synopsis>《恐 龙 快 打》又 称《恐 龙 新 世 纪》，承 载 了 许 多 80 后 的 童 年 回 忆。

作 品 中 的 道 具 较 以 往 同 类 作 品 有 很 大 的 强 化。比 如 木 桶 一 类 的 容 器 道 具，除 了 砸 破 后 可 以 得 到 其 中 的 物 品，还 可 以 被 角 色 抬 起 作 为 投 掷 道 具。又 比 如 所 有 的 枪 械 道 具 都 有 弹 药 的 概 念，弹 药 用 完 就 只 能 作 为 一 次 性 的 投 掷 道 具 了，玩 家 甚 至 还 可 以 抢 到 敌 人 的 武 器 来 反 制。

除 了 普 通 攻 击、快 跑 中 的 重 击、两 键 齐 按 的 去 血 保 命 绝 招，配 合 方 向 键，还 能 使 出 各 种 大 招 和 摔 技。

游 戏 改 编 自 1986 年 的 美 国 漫 画《Xenozoic Tales》，中 文 名《新 侏 罗 纪 神 话》，讲 述 由 于 全 球 气 候 变 暖，海 平 面 上 升，人 类 不 得 已 躲 入 深 埋 地 下 的 Vault 避 难 所 以 求 生 存。

到 了 公 元 26 世 纪，地 表 恢 复 到 适 宜 居 住 的 状 态，人 类 再 次 回 到 地 面，发 现 恐 龙 因 全 球 变 暖 和 生 态 好 转 再 次 出 现。人 们 对 于 恐 龙 的 看 法 不 一，一 些 人 认 为 应 该 和 恐 龙 和 谐 共 存，另 一 些 人 则 以 猎 杀 或 抓 捕 恐 龙 牟 利。

主 角 Jack 住 在 纽 约，是 坚 定 的“人 龙 共 存 派”，为 了 保 护 恐 龙，常 与 恐 龙 猎 人 发 生 冲 突。Jack 的 爱 好 是 收 集 和 修 复 经 典 的 20 世 纪 美 制 凯 迪 拉 克 轿 车，但 由 于 石 油 的 枯 竭 亦 或 是 炼 油 技 术 的 丧 失，他 必 须 使 用 恐 龙 提 取 液 作 为 车 子 的 替 代 能 源。

2513 年，针 对 恐 龙 的 盗 猎 活 动 突 然 猛 增，Jack 和 他 的 朋 友 们 决 定 一 查 到 底，发 现 其 中 有 远 比 投 机 买 卖 更 大 的 阴 谋。原 来，疯 狂 科 学 家 Fessenden 博 士 想 通 过 基 因 工 程，研 究 恐 龙 以 获 得 征 服 世 界 的 力 量。他 通 过 黑 市 交 易 购 买 恐 龙 就 是 为 了 获 取 实 验 样 品。他 不 仅 制 造、控 制 恐 龙，而 且 还 研 究 如 何 将 人 和 恐 龙 合 体，创 造 攻 击 力 超 强 的 变 异 怪 物。

游 戏 的 四 个 主 角 得 知 了 博 士 的 计 划 后，开 着 凯 迪 拉 克 轿 车，一 路 奋 战，打 败 了 博 士 众 多 的 手 下，杀 死 已 变 异 的 邪 恶 博 士，并 触 发 了 位 于 纽 约 地 下，由 原 Vault 避 难 所 改 造 而 成 的 博 士 实 验 室 自 毁。</synopsis>
		<genre>清版动作</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1993" month="05" day="20"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="15">
		</rating>
		<input players="3">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Captain Commando">
		<id>37358A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Captain Commando</title>
	<synopsis>Captain Commando is set in a crime-ridden future in the year 2026, where a superhero named Captain Commando, assisted by his three faithful Commando Companions rise up to protect the Earth and all the Galaxy from a gang of super-powered criminals.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>名将</title>
		<synopsis>《名 将》这 款 游 戏 的 平 衡 性 较 强，难 度 适 中，节 奏 爽 快，讲 究 配 合，最 多 支 持 4 人 同 时 游 戏，每 个 角 色 都 个 性 鲜 明，拥 有 独 一 无 二 的 招 式。

这 款 风 靡 一 时 的 街 机 清 版 动 作 游 戏，是 卡 普 空 公 司 的 原 创 作 品，当 年 还 有 漫 画 同 步 发 行，《突 击 队 长》才 是 它 的 正 确 名 字，但 是 因 为 漫 画 并 未 传 入 国 内，所 以 很 多 玩 家 并 不 知 晓。

故 事 讲 述 的 是 公 元 2026 年，地 球 上 恶 势 力 横 行，罪 犯 们 大 多 拥 有 常 人 所 没 有 的 特 殊 能 力 和 高 科 技 武 器。一 支 由 木 乃 伊、警 察、忍 者 和 天 才 儿 童 组 成 的 特 种 部 队 奋 起 反 抗，与 超 能 力 犯 罪 集 团 展 开 斗 争。

在 游 戏 过 程 中，主 角 可 以 坐 上 巨 大 的 步 行 机 与 敌 人 作 战，步 行 机 虽 然 威 力 巨 大，但 是 由 于 体 积 巨 大，而 且 行 动 迟 缓，被 攻 击 的 可 能 性 也 大 大 增 加，这 种“坐 骑”的 设 计 概 念 被 以 后 很 多 作 品 所 借 鉴。

除 了 游 戏 画 面 和 操 作 手 感 上 的 巨 大 进 步，《名 将》还 将《快 打 旋 风》开 创 的“摆 拳”玩 法 进 一 步 发 扬 光 大，无 论 什 么 Boss，都 可 以 用 一 套 摆 拳 直 接 连 死。</synopsis>
		<genre>清版动作</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1991" month="09" day="28"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="18">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Carrier Air Wing">
		<id>37359A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Carrier Air Wing</title>
	<synopsis>Carrier Air Wing / U.S. Navy is a horizontally-scrolling shoot-em-up for one or two players set in the 1990s, a decade of great change marked by growing friendships between old enemies and never before seen levels of co-operation between powerful nations of the world. However, in 1997, using new weapons designed in secrecy, the Middle Eastern country of 'Rabu' threatens to destroy this new and fragile peace. 

Players chose to pilot any one of three different jet fighters and must battle their way through ten enemy-packed stages. Each fighter has a fuel bar which is full at the start of each stage but gradually decreases, additional fuel is lost each time the fighter takes damage from an enemy.</synopsis>
	<genre>Horizontally scrolling shooters</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>飞空之翼</title>
		<synopsis>在本作诞生之前，卡普空原本是想制作一款《战区88》的续编作品，但由于未能取得相关版权，制作人只好修改计划，制作成内容独立的原创作品。
《雌虎战机》沿袭了《战区88》的佣兵制系统，每一关消灭Boss后获得的金钱，可以用来购买和升级各种武器装备，还是可以用来购买加长生命的血槽。
游戏剧情中，X国的兵器大体上以苏联兵器为主题，也使用了一部分诸如隐形战斗机、早期警戒机等美国兵器。</synopsis>
		<genre>横向卷轴射击</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1990" month="10" day="30"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="17">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Dynasty Wars">
		<id>41078A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Dynasty Wars</title>
	<synopsis>This game is a side-scrolling beat-em-up based on Japanese manga books of the same name and is a re-enactment of the historical battles between the Kingdom of Shu and the Yellow Turban rebels. Up to two players assume the roles of one of the four Chinese generals riding on horseback whose goal is to wipe out the 'Huang Ching', the organization responsible for the unrest of the Han Dynasty, and to eventually defeat the tyrant, Dong Zhuo.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>吞食天地1 王朝战争</title>
		<genre>清版动作</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1989" month="04" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="16">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Final Fight">
		<id>37362A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Final Fight</title>
	<synopsis>Final Crash is a bootleg of Capcom's "Final Fight"</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>快打旋风</title>
		<genre>清版动作</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1989" month="11" day="25"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="16">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Forgotten Worlds">
		<id>37363A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Forgotten Worlds</title>
	<synopsis>The planet used to be beautiful, with gorgeous cities and gleaming countrysides. Until the Aliens attacked! With fire, bombs, and napalm they devastated the world! They made the planet so abominable that it became an outcast in the universe - the Forgotten World. Until you, the Nameless One, appear. You're a Super Warrior of incredible power and energy. You make it your business to reclaim the panet for its rightful owners - the Human Beings!</synopsis>
	<genre>Horizontally scrolling shooters</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>失落的世界</title>
		<genre>横向卷轴射击</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1988" month="07" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="13">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Ghouls'n Ghosts">
		<id>41441A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Ghouls'n Ghosts</title>
	<synopsis>Three years have passed since the events of "Makaimura" and Arthur the knight once again finds himself battling against the hideous creatures of Demon World. The demons have now seized the kingdom and Arthur returns home to witness the castle's lone survivor, his beloved Gunievere, murdered by the king of the demons, Lucifer. Arthur once again embarks on a one-man quest to destroy the demonic invaders and save Gunievere's mortal soul. </synopsis>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>大魔界村</title>
		<genre>平台</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1988" month="10" day="05"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="18">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="The King of Dragons">
		<id>37366A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>The King of Dragons</title>
	<synopsis>The King of Dragons is a 1991 side-scrolling hack and slash video game by Capcom that allows players to choose from five characters (Elf, Wizard, Fighter, Cleric, and Dwarf) in order to travel through the kingdom of Malus and defeat the monsters that have taken over, as well as their leader, the red dragon Gildiss. Like Capcom's Knights of the Round, it features a level advancement system, allowing character attributes to be upgraded as players progress through the game. The setting is very similar to that of Dungeons &amp; Dragons and other medieval fantasy worlds, with familiar monsters such as Orcs, Gnolls, Harpies, Wyverns, Cyclopes, and Minotaurs.

The game was ported to the Super NES and released in 1994. An emulated version of the game was released as part of Capcom Classics Collection Vol. 2 and Capcom Classics Collection: Reloaded.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ES">
	<synopsis>The King of Dragons es un juego de 1991 que permite a los jugadores elegir entre cinco personajes (Elfo, Mago, Luchador, Clérigo y Enano) para viajar por el reino de Malus y derrotar a los monstruos que han asumido el control, así como su líder, el dragón rojo Gildiss. Al igual que Knights of the Round de Capcom, cuenta con un sistema de avance de nivel, permitiendo que los atributos de los personajes sean actualizados a medida que los jugadores avanzan a través del juego. El escenario es muy similar al de Dungeons &amp; Dragons y otros mundos de fantasía medieval, con monstruos familiares como Orcos, Gnomos, Arpías, Wyverns, Cíclopes y Minotauros. El juego fue portado a Super NES y lanzado en 1994. Una versión emulada del juego fue lanzada como parte de Capcom Classics Collection Vol. 2 y Capcom Classics Colección: Reloaded.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="FR">
	<synopsis>The King of Dragons est un beat'em all original qui reprend les éléments classiques de l'heroic fantasy. Le Grand Royaume est en très mauvaise posture : Gildiss, un dragon rouge, ancien et très maléfique, a décidé de l'envahir. Heureusement, une équipe de 5 héros se décide à l'affronter : le rapide elfe et son arc magique, le puissant mage et ses sortilèges, le chevalier tout en force, le prête-guerrier qui progresse vite en puissance et enfin le nain rapide muni de sa fidèle hache. The King of Dragons rappelle fortement Golden Axe ! Il faut dire que le thème du jeu (l'heroic fantasy) et la vue de trois quarts y sont pour beaucoup. Pour changer, les tableaux de The King of Dragons ne sont pas très longs, mais cela est compensé par la difficulté posée par les habituels monstres de fin de niveau. Ces derniers ne sont d'ailleurs pas loin d'être plus nombreux que les monstres que l'on rencontre durant le jeu ! Rappelons qu'il y a 16 niveaux, donc 16 gros monstres !</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="DE">
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="PT">
	<synopsis>The King of Dragons é um jogo de 1991, que permite aos jogadores escolher entre cinco personagens (Elfo, Mago, Lutador, Clérigo e Anão) para viajar pelo reino de Malus e derrotar os monstros que assumiram, assim como seu líder, o dragão vermelho Gildiss. Como os Cavaleiros da Távola da Capcom, ele possui um sistema de avanço de nível, permitindo que os atributos de caráter sejam atualizados à medida que os jogadores progridem no jogo. A configuração é muito semelhante à de Dungeons &amp; Dragons e outros mundos de fantasia medieval, com monstros familiares como Orcs, Gnolls, Harpies, Wyverns, Cyclopes e Minotaurs.
O jogo foi portado para o Super NES e lançado em 1994. Uma versão emulada do jogo foi lançado como parte da Capcom Classics Collection Vol. 2 e Capcom Classics Coleção: Reloaded.</synopsis>
	<genre>Briga de rua,Luta / 2.5D,Luta</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>龙王战士</title>
		<genre>清版动作</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1991" month="08" day="05"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="12">
		</rating>
		<input players="3">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Knights of the Round">
		<id>42020A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Knights of the Round</title>
	<synopsis>Knights of the Round is an arcade game released by Capcom in 1991. A side-scrolling beat 'em up based loosely on the legend of King Arthur and the Knights of the Round Table, the game features an role-playing video game-like level advancement system, with fighters getting new weapons and armour as they advance through the game, however the player can not choose how to upgrade his/her character - the level up system is static.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ES">
	<synopsis>Knights of the Round es un juego de arcade lanzado por Capcom en 1991. Un beat 'em up de desplazamiento lateral basado libremente en la leyenda del Rey Arturo y los Caballeros de la Mesa Redonda, el juego presenta un nivel similar al de un videojuego de rol. sistema de avance, con luchadores que obtienen nuevas armas y armaduras a medida que avanzan en el juego; sin embargo, el jugador no puede elegir cómo actualizar su personaje: el sistema de subir de nivel es estático.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="FR">
	<synopsis>Dans ce beat'em up médiéval, vous pouvez incarner Lancelot, Arthur ou Perceval (jusqu'à trois players simultanés). Nos trois chevaliers devront parcourir plusieurs niveaux d'une beauté rare remplis d'ennemis aussi laids que bien faits. La jouabilité est de mise dans ce jeu, et vous risquez de rester longtemps devant votre écran rien que pour le plaisir des yeux.
A ne pas manquer !!!</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat'em All</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="DE">
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="PT">
	<synopsis>Knights of the Round é um jogo de arcade lançado pela Capcom em 1991. Um side-scrolling beat 'em up baseado livremente sobre a lenda do Rei Arthur e os Cavaleiros da Tábula Redonda, o jogo apresenta um sistema avançado de melhorias no estilo RPG, com os lutadores obtendo novas armas e armaduras confome avançam através do jogo, no entanto, o jogador não pode escolher como atualizar seu personagem - sistema de melhorias é estático.</synopsis>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>圆桌骑士</title>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1991" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="15">
		</rating>
		<input players="3">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Magic Sword - Heroic Fantasy">
		<id>57920A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Magic Sword - Heroic Fantasy</title>
	<synopsis>The land has been cast in darkness by Drokmar, who has been corrupted by the Black Orb; an artefact that promises immortality to anyone who comes under the influence of the orb's powerful sorcery. Tw</synopsis>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>魔法剑 英雄的幻想</title>
		<genre>平台</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1990" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="18">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Mega Man - The Power Battle">
		<id>78892A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Mega Man - The Power Battle</title>
	<synopsis>Have you ever pictured a Rockman or Megaman game that allows to skip all the platform elements and just grapple against the bosses? That's pretty much the main idea in this game! Choose from Rockman/Megaman, Protoman or Bass and battle against classic bosses in the series. Features great 2-D graphics, solid control, and a nice use of strategy (since the right order of weapons will rid you of specific enemies in no time!).</synopsis>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>洛克人1 力量之战</title>
		<genre>格斗</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1995" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="15">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Mega Twins">
		<id>37371A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Mega Twins</title>
	<synopsis>The game features two twins who are attempting to re-take control of their land, Alurea, after a monster unexpectedly attacks, destroying everything in its path. The people of Alurea have lived in peace for a thousand years and have forgotten how to fight, yet the land's only survivors, the twin sons of the king, must take up the challenge and return their kingdom to its former glory. The two twins, aged around 15 at the time the game takes place, venture forth in search of a legendary stone known as "Dragon Blue Eyes", which is rumored to be able to put everything back to rights.</synopsis>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>双麒儿</title>
		<genre>平台</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1990" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="16">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Mercs">
		<id>78903A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Mercs</title>
	<synopsis>The US faces a grave crisis! The former president has been kidnapped by a group of revolutionaries while on a trip on Central Africa meant to promote world peace. Take control of three highly skilled anti-terrorist soldiers and venture through enemy lines to save the former president &amp; annihilate the rebel army in the process. Features solid graphics &amp; sound, plenty of weapons &amp; vehicles to use and hulking bosses to defeat.</synopsis>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>战场之狼2</title>
		<genre>射击</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1990" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="18">
		</rating>
		<input players="3">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
			<control type="coop" required="true"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Muscle Bomber Duo - Ultimate Team Battle">
		<id>37367A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Muscle Bomber Duo - Ultimate Team Battle</title>
	<synopsis>Professional wrestling experienced a sudden increase in popularity during the early 1980s, where many professional wrestling organizations were started all over the world. A severe rivalry existed among the organizations.

In order to resolve this conflict, 8 organizations combined to form the Capcom Professional Wrestling Association (CPWA), led by Victor Ortega, the CPWA?s first champion.

One day, Ortega suddenly vanished. He was considered to be the axis of the sport and his unexpected disappearance caused the CPWA to enter an age of confusion and disorder. The BPWA, a dark underground wrestling organization, chose to take advantage of this opportunity and began moving. With "Fighters of Muscle Bomber = Destiny" as the theme, the CPWA chief executives decided to hold a world tour called the ?Crash Carnival,? to decide the new king of the CPWA.

The gong that determines the new ?Master of Muscle Bomber? is sounded?</synopsis>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>摔角霸王1 最终之战</title>
		<genre>格斗</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1993" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="16">
		</rating>
		<input players="4">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Nemo">
		<id>37372A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Nemo</title>
	<synopsis>One night, as Nemo sleeps, he is visited in a dream by the King of Slumberland, who invites Nemo to come and play with the King's daughter, the Princess. Nemo finds himself unable to find the Princess however, so he and 'Flip', a strange companion who also turns up in the dream, decide to explore Slumberland and find the king.

Nemo is a colourful and abstract platform shoot-em-up set in the dream world of Slumberland, a surreal world in which childrens' toys are running amok and must be destroyed. Nemo is armed with a magical staff that emits a burst of magic to destroy the many enemies, some of which require multiple hits. A number of power-ups also appear at regular intervals to aid Nemo in his quest through seven tough stages.</synopsis>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>梦幻冒险</title>
		<genre>平台</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1990" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="18">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Pang! 3">
		<id>37373A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Pang! 3</title>
	<synopsis>Pang! 3 is the second sequel to the superb 1989 original, Pang! 3 retains the same gameplay of its predecessors but adds vastly improved graphics and a choice of three difficulty levels; Beginner, Normal and Panic. On both the 'Normal' and 'Panic' skill levels, players can choose from 4 different playable characters; each possessing different strengths and weaknesses, such as a double harpoon or quick shots. On the beginner level, players can only use the Mexican character.

Another notable difference is in the game's use of backdrops: instead of the world landmarks of the first two games, Pang! 3 features classical works of art in the form of paintings and sculptures.</synopsis>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>魔鬼气泡3</title>
		<genre>射击</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Mitchell</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1995" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="17">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Pnickies">
		<id>37374A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Pnickies</title>
	<synopsis>A falling blocks game released only to arcades. Like-colored blocks merge together and more points are awarded for larger masses.</synopsis>
	<genre>Puzzle</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>魔法方块</title>
		<genre>益智</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1994" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="14">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="The Punisher">
		<id>37375A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>The Punisher</title>
	<synopsis>A Capcom arcade beat-em-up game similar to games like Double Dragon featuring the Marvel character The Punisher. Nick Fury is also a playable character in this game.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ES">
	<synopsis>Un juego de arcade de Capcom, similar a juegos como Double Dragon con el personaje de Marvel The Punisher. Nick Fury es también un personaje que se puede jugar en este juego.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="FR">
	<synopsis>The punisher est un beat them all très beau graphiquement avec de nombreux coups de nombreuses armes ( batte de base ball ; pistolet ; lance flamme ; etc... ) avec un décor déstructible un nombre important d'ennemis ce jeu sert a se défouler à coup de poing ,de grenades et j'en passe, donc ce jeu est à telecharger pour les amateurs du genre les fans de "the punisher" où les personnages sont très bien modélisé est à ceux qui ont les nerfs et qui aimeré ce lacher un peu sur un jeu.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat'em All</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="DE">
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="PT">
	<synopsis>The Punisher é um jogo arcade, beat 'em up,desenvolvido e lançado pela Capcom em 1993. Ele estrela o anti-herói da Marvel Comics o Punisher e co-estrela da S.H.I.E.L.D., o Agente Nick Fury, como o personagem do segundo jogador juntos embarcam em uma missão para matar o senhor do crime o Kingpin e derrubar sua organização. Apesar de seguir a mesma fórmula geral que o anterior beat 'em ups da Capcom, o jogo tem uma gama de armas utilizáveis ??e uma apresentação em estilo de quadrinhos</synopsis>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>惩罚者</title>
		<genre>清版动作</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1993" month="04" day="22"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="17">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Quiz &amp; Dragons">
		<id>42583A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Quiz &amp; Dragons</title>
	<synopsis>The game plays similar to a board game, where the player is given a predetermined dice roll that moves the player up to six spaces on the board; however, if the player is so given the choice, he can move to a space of his choosing if there is a fork in the road. After landing on a space, the player is given a series of questions (the amount of questions needed to be answered increase as the game progresses) in order to proceed back to the board for another dice roll. The player is given a time limit to answer the question, with points given that vary based on how fast the player answered the question correctly. If the player is successful in answering a question, one of the orbs above the enemy's portrait will light up, indicating a correct answer. If the player answers a question incorrectly, he will lose a life point. if the player loses all life points, the player must continue within the time limit or else the game is over.</synopsis>
	<genre>English Quiz</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>龙之迷题</title>
		<genre>英语问答</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1992" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="14">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Quiz Tonosama no Yabou 2 - Zenkoku-ban">
		<id>42606A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Quiz Tonosama no Yabou 2 - Zenkoku-ban</title>
	<synopsis>Quiz Tonosama no Yabou 2 - Zenkoku-ban is a feudal Japanese quiz game from Capcom.</synopsis>
	<genre>Japanese Quiz</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>城主的野心问答2 全国版</title>
		<genre>日语问答</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1995" month="" day=""/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="10">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Saturday Night Slam Masters">
		<id>37379A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Saturday Night Slam Masters</title>
	<synopsis>A 1-on-1 fighting game in which players choose from 10 different wrestlers and take to the ring to try and defeat their larger-than-life opponents. Each wrestler has an assortment of moves, including his own special 'super slam'. The object of the game is to win and defend the championship by pinning or putting a submission hold on your opponent.</synopsis>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>摔角霸王1</title>
		<genre>格斗</genre>
	</locale>	
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1993" month="07" day="13"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="18">
		</rating>
		<input players="4">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Street Fighter II' - Hyper Fighting">
		<id>37378A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Street Fighter II' - Hyper Fighting</title>
	<synopsis>Street Fighter II' - Hyper Fighting is the second SFII follow-up. Here's what's new: 
Gameplay is SIGNIFICANTLY sped up to intensify the pace of the game. 
More special moves (ie. Chun Li's fireball, Dhalsim's Yoga Teleport) are added for each character except for M. Bison. 
New color schemes are added for each character (but the color schemes for the stage backgrounds are still the same as they were for Champion Edition). 
The addition of mid-air special moves for Chun Li, Ryu and Ken are introduced. 
Platform graphics (resembling the medal ceremonies in the Olympics) are added to each character's ending, featuring the character you completed the game with at the first-place platform, M. Bison at the second-place platform, and Sagat at the third-place platform. The musical setting for this display is the music from the home stage of the character standing on the 1st-place platform (If you completed the game with Sagat or M. Bison, the one you used stands on the 1st-place platform, the other one on the 2nd-place platform, and Vega occupies the 3rd-place platform).</synopsis>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>街头霸王2 究极格斗</title>
		<genre>格斗</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1992" month="12" day="10"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="17">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Street Fighter II - The World Warrior">
		<id>42982A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Street Fighter II - The World Warrior</title>
	<synopsis>GET READY TO RUMBLE!

From across the globe comes eight of the wildest fighters the world has ever known. Choose your champion, gather your courage and prepare to battle your opponents in a bare knuckle brawl. Face Ken and his devastating "Dragon Punch"! Watch the temperature rise as Dhalsim incinerates you with his mystical Yoga Flame! Hear your spine crack as Zangief smashes you to the pavement with his spinning pile driver! Cover your ears as Guile breaks the sound barrier with the awesome power of the Sonic Boom!

Annihilate your competition and claim the right to test your skills against the bone-crushing power of the Grand Masters! Can you survive? Can Anyone?</synopsis>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>街头霸王2 天下斗士</title>
		<genre>格斗</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1991" month="02" day="05"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="17">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Street Fighter II' - Champion Edition">
		<id>37377A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Street Fighter II' - Champion Edition</title>
	<synopsis>From the corners of the globe come twelve of the toughest fighters to ever prowl the streets. Choose your champion and step into the arena as one of the eight original challengers or as one of the four Grand Masters! Pound your opponent as Balrog and knock them out for the count. Tower over your prey as Sagat and daze them with your awesome Tiger Shot. Slash your opponent with Vega's claw and send them running for cover. Or strike fear into your enemies as M. Bison, the greatest Grand Master of them all!</synopsis>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>街头霸王2 冠军版</title>
		<genre>格斗</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1992" month="03" day="18"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="18">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Street Fighter Zero">
		<id>64254A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Street Fighter Zero</title>
	<synopsis>The game introduces several new features, expanding on the Super Combo system previously featured in Super Street Fighter II Turbo, with graphics drawn in the same cartoonish style Capcom employed in Darkstalkers and X-Men: Children of the Atom.[2][3] The plot of Street Fighter Alpha is set after the original Street Fighter but before Street Fighter II and thus the game features younger versions of established characters, as well as characters from the original Street Fighter and Final Fight, and a few who are new to the series.</synopsis>
	<genre>Fighting</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>少年街霸1</title>
		<genre>格斗</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1995" month="01" day="20"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="18">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Strider">
		<id>37380A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Strider</title>
	<synopsis>Strider is a multi-directional scrolling platform beat-em-up in which the player takes control of 'Strider Hiryu', a ninja-style warrior who must defeat a legendary being known as 'Grandmaster Meio'. 

Set in a dystopian future in the year 2048, Meio has been watching Earth from his own distant galaxy and has created a space station (known as 'The Third Moon') between Earth and its moon in order to rule over the Human race. </synopsis>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ES">
	<synopsis>En 2048, un Hiryu Strider llamado Hiryu viaja por el mundo en busca del misterioso Meio, que reina en la Tierra desde su base lunar, y controla a Hiryu, armado con su espada Falchion, a través de cinco niveles que van desde la Unión Soviética hasta la selva tropical. Hiryu tiene la particularidad de ser capaz de colgarse en las paredes gracias a un gancho de metal, y también puede ser ayudado por dos animales robóticos (un halcón y un tigre).</synopsis>
	<genre>Plataforma / Beat'em Up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="FR">
	<synopsis>En 2048, un Strider nommé Hiryu parcourt le monde à la recherche du mystérieux Meio, qui règne sur la Terre depuis sa base lunaire.Le joueur contrôle Hiryu, armé de son sabre Falchion, à travers cinq niveaux allant de l'Union Soviétique à la forêt vierge. Hiryu a la particularité de pouvoir s'accrocher aux parois grâce à un crochet métallique, et peut également se faire aider de deux animaux robotiques (un faucon et un tigre) appelés Options.</synopsis>
	<genre>Plateforme / Beat'em Up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="DE">
	<genre>Plattform / Beat'em Up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="PT">
	<synopsis>Strider é um jogo de videogame da Capcom, lançado em 1989 o enredo do jogo é este: Em 2048, a Terra está sob ameaça de Grandmaster Meio, um ser de outra galáxia, que intenciona dominar o nosso planeta. Para tanto, Meio construirá uma estação estelar, localizada entre a Terra e a Lua, denominada de "Third Moon" (trad: Terceira Lua).
Todavia, Hiryu, um valente guerreiro Strider, armado com sua poderosa espada cypher, decide opor-se a Meio, combatendo suas forças invasoras. Sozinho nesta luta, Hiryu receberá apenas a ajuda dos "Options" (pequenos robôs, ou ainda animais mecânicos, como uma águia e uma pantera) que ele, eventualmente, venha a encontrar pelo seu caminho.</synopsis>
	<genre>Plataforma / Beat'em Up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="JA">
	<title>Strider Hiryu</title>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>出击飞龙</title>
		<title>平台</title>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1989" month="03" day="07"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="17">
		</rating>
		<input players="1">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Warriors of Fate">
		<id>44111A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Warriors of Fate</title>
	<synopsis>Warriors of Fate is a side-scrolling beat 'em up produced by Capcom, first released as a coin-operated arcade game in 1992 and later ported to the Sega Saturn and Sony PlayStation. It is Capcom's third game based on the Tenchi wo Kurau manga, following Dynasty Wars and Destiny of an Emperor.</synopsis>
	<genre>Beat 'em up</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>吞食天地2 赤壁之战</title>
		<genre>清版动作</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1992" month="09" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="12">
		</rating>
		<input players="3">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Three Wonders">
		<id>37357A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Three Wonders</title>
	<synopsis>The main character of the Chariot and Midnight Wanderers games Lou, was used as an assist only character for Marvel vs Capcom he also had the option character from Midnight Wanderers known as Firestorm with him. His sprite is like an enlarged version of his sprites from Midnight Wanderers, he shares the same position stance, his trademark jump in which he holds his hand on his hat, and also the same shooting animation. The sprites are recoloured in a more vibrant cartoon-esque style, as opposed to the washed out effect from the games, to match the style of the Marvel vs Capcom series. If two players get Lou, then the second player's pallette is Green, and is most likely based on Siva's color clothing from the Midnight Wanderers game. Player two's firestorm is colored orange.

Lou's Companion Siva, has a character based on him as a tribute, featuring on Capcom's Cannon Spike game. The character is called Shiba Shintaro.</synopsis>
	<genre>Compilation</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>奇迹三世界</title>
		<genre>合集</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1991" month="07" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="14">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="U.N. Squadron">
		<id>43837A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>U.N. Squadron</title>
	<synopsis>U.N. Squadron / Area 88 is a horizontally-scrolling shoot-em-up and is based on the Manga series of the same name. The game features characters from the original Manga and their mission is to battle their way through enemy-packed levels to stop a terrorist group known as 'Project 4'.</synopsis>
	<genre>Horizontally scrolling shooters</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>战区88</title>
		<genre>横向卷轴射击</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1989" month="08" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="14">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Varth - Operation Thunderstorm">
		<id>37382A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Varth - Operation Thunderstorm</title>
	<synopsis>Varth: Operation Thunderstorm is an arcade game in the vertical scrolling shooter genre, published in 1992. The game did not see a console port following its initial release, but 14 years later Digital Eclipse Software would port the game onto the PlayStation 2, PSP and Xbox as part of the Capcom Classics Collection Vol. 2.</synopsis>
	<genre>Vertically scrolling shooters</genre>
	</locale>	
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>威虎战机 雷暴行动</title>
		<genre>纵向卷轴射击</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
		<date year="1992" month="07" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="14">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
	<game name="Willow">
		<id>37383A</id>
	<locale lang="EN">
	<title>Willow</title>
	<synopsis>Willow is a sideways scrolling platform shoot-em-up game loosely based upon the movie of the same name. Players take on the role of one of two characters: Willow Ufgood or Madmartigan. The hero's mission is to rescue the baby Elora Danan from the evil Queen Bavmorda and bring her back safely. If the quest fails, the Queen will plunge the world into darkness and chaos.

The game consists of 6 levels, each representing a scene from the movie. Defeated enemies drop gold coins that can be collected by the player. In addition, each level is littered with locked treasure chests that can be shot open and the treasure within collected. The gold can be used to purchase a number of weapons and character power-ups from a nearby shop (represented on screen by a wise old man). All power-ups will stay with the player until all lives are lost and the game is over.</synopsis>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	</locale>
	<locale lang="ZHCN">
		<title>威洛之旅</title>
		<genre>平台</genre>
	</locale>
		<developer>Capcom</developer>
		<publisher>Lucasfilm</publisher>
		<date year="1989" month="06" day="01"/>
		<rating type="NOTE" value="16">
		</rating>
		<input players="2">
			<control type="wiimote" required="true"/>
			<control type="nunchuk" required="false"/>
			<control type="classiccontroller" required="false"/>
			<control type="gamecube" required="false"/>
		</input>
	</game>
</datafile>
